Guide to the Center for Instructional Development and Distance Education (CIDDE), University of Pittsburgh, Photograph Collection, 1986-2005 UA.15.38.1
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographer, 1986-2005; I.
  - Photographer: Herb Ferguson, 1958-1996
    - Women's gymnastics team photo, January 20, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Dave Havern, January 26, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Gene Raynak (Posthumous degree in engineering), February 1, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Big East swim meet, February 25, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Big East swimming and diving, February 24-26, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Linda Hoye, state presentation, March 2, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Distance learning class, March 2, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Electrical engineering scholarship award, March 17, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Engineering awards banquet, March 23, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Engineering class, March 24, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Chocolate festival, March 31, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Pitt Ambassadors dinner, April 6, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Cheerleaders, April 13, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Orthodontic residents, April 14, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Katz graduate school of business luncheon, April 18, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Patrick Polk, April 19, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Alumni leadership conference, May 5-6, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Day care center, Clyde St. new facilities, May 12, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Chemical engineering portraits, May 16, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Dr. Higman (Neurology) retirement dinner, May 20, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Check presentation, July 13, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Dr. Lunsford's (neurosurgery) birthday party, July 25, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Charles Connick, designer of Heinz windows, July 25, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Robert Mollenhauer, institutional advancement, July 28, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Chemical engineering portraits, August 1, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Professor and student, Graduate School of Public Health lobby, August 8, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Women, Infants, and Children (WIC) Program, August 8, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Stephen Foster Memorial, Dean Root, August 20, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Cross country team, August 22, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Football stadium improvements, August 26, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Graham Park convocation, August 26, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Dr. Ness and Dr. Hughey (Graduate School of Public Health), August 28, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Computing and Information Systems facilities, August 30, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Dr. and Mrs. Nordenberg, September 1, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Day of Caring, September 15, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Crawford Village and street photos (USCUR), September 15, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Partners Progress luncheon, September 18, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Chang Benedict, International Management and Development Institute (IMDI), September 18, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Volunteer fair, September 18, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Lois Jones art show, September 21, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Women's gymnastics, September 28, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - EET brochure, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Portraits of four professors from Katz Graduate School of Business, October 31, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Gastroenterology and heptology brochure, November 8, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Law class reunion 1960-1965, November 11, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Law intellectual property Continuing Legal Education program, November 11, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Katz Graduate School of Business dinner, November 12, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Track team seniors, November 27, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Football facilities, November 29, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Portrait and classroom (Katz Graduate School of Business), November 30, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Center for Public and Community Service program, December 4, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Heinz Chapel Christmas concert, December 5, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Pennsylvania Hall, December 6, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Heinz Chapel Christmas concert, December 18, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Men's basketball, Pitt vs. University of North Carolina-Chapel Hill, December 20, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Lothrop fitness center, January 5, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Engineering, VA Hospital, and nursing facilities, January 17, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Women's basketball, January 24, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Professor Puzzle (outreach program) at Vam Elementary School, February 22, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Forbes Tower, February 27, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Old Campus Panoramas, March 1, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Bigelow Boulevard closing, March 1, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Pitt Moms' Society group photos, March 26, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Toni Bearman, Dean of School of Information Sciences, April 1, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Distinguished faculty reception, April 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Kindergarteners playing with robots, April 18, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Rowing team, May 7, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Rich Boyd, Chief of campus police, May 15, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Civil engineering professor in class, May 21, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - McCormick Hall ID Center, May 30, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Austrian Room dedication, June 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Austrian Room, June 13, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Dental School exhibit, June 10, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Masters of Business Administration golf outing, June 17, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Orthodontics professors, July, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Athletic department staff, July 8, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Athletic department staged photos, July 11, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Athletic department counselors, July 11, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Phillipa Benson and Laurel Roberts, staff photos, biology, July 23, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Trish White, department of communications, July 25, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Football team, August 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Dr. George Chambers, President of Greensburg campus, August 19, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Men's soccer team, August 21, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Katz School of Business, August 27, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Women's basketball team, August 28, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Football kickoff luncheon, August 30, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Women's basketball, September 5, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Syria-Lebanon Room, September 8, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Senate Council meeting, September 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Day of Caring, September 11, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Tim Karen Scholarship Award, September 14, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Women's gymnastics, September 19, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Director of Manufacturing Assistance Center, name unknown, September 20, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Women's soccer, first game played in stadium, September 21, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Pitt Ambassador golf outing, September 30, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Wrestling team, October 1, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Engineering professors in their labs, October 2, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Management Program for Executives, October 3, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Pharmacy homecoming speakers, October 4, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Scholarship students, Katz School of Business, October 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Lanuage disorder faculty and staff, October 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Basketball managers, October 22, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Steve Pederson, new athletic director, October 28, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Rachel Petrucelli, distinguished lecturer, nursing, October 30, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Race car at football game, October 31, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Cheerleaders, October 31, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Distinguished engineering awards, November 1, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Dental school portraits, November 13, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Human Resources training class, November 20, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Heinz Chapel Christmas concert, December 3, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - School of Health and Rehabilitation Sciences check presentation, December 3, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - School of Engineering reunion, September, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Photographer: Gary Guydosh, 1995-1997
    - Campus stock photos for University Times, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - New Faculty Dinner, August 30, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Dr. Chang, School of Engineering, September 1, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Women's volleyball, August 25, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Richard Sotak, September 12, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dr. S. Adler, September 8, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Pharmacy School head shots, August 24, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Chern, August 25, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - SI Plus lunch, August 26, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - International Management and Development Institute (IMDI) group, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Katz Graduate School of Business alumni dinner, October 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Dr. Pat Kochanek, September 2, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Terry Schwinghammer (School of Pharmacy), September 8, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Karen Snyder (School of Pharmacy), September 9, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Men's and Women's swim teams, September 9, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Pittsburgh Coal Conference (School of Engineering), September 15, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Student Organization Meeting (School of Engineering), September 16, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Chancellor's Circle, September 24, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Dr. Barbara Barnes, September 21, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Dr. Anhalt, October 4, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Jonathan Harris reception, September 20, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - School of Health and Rehabilitation Science homecoming brunch, September 19, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - School of Health and Rehabilitation Science homecoming brunch, October 15, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Visiting Nurses Association, October 5, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Arts and Sciences 30 year reunion, October 13, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Dr. K. Lewis (School of Engineering), September 22, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - School of Engineering Student Council, September 22, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Dr. Simon, September 29, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - College of General Studies new lounge, September 26, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - School of Engineering soils lab, September 21, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - School of Engineering electronics lab, September 27, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Dr. Kelly Kellecher, September 28, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - School of Engineering exchange students, September 28, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - School of Engineering electronics staff, September 28, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - School of Engineering electronics lab, September 28, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Florence Nightingale, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Freshman move in, August 26, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Greek rush party, September 30, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Gymnastics, September 30, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Meg and her daughter, October 5, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - School of Pharmacy career day, October 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - School of Medicine group, October 4, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Pitt Tac Toe, October 12, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Pharmacology brochure, October 5, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Women's basketball team, October 5, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - IMDI group, October 8, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Mayor Tom Murphy in class, October 4, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Sports Illo campus fest, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - School of Engineering race car at stadium, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Freddie, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - School of Medicine pin and newsletter, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Dr. R. Musgrave, October 10, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Dr. Wang, October 11, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Jessica Brimecambe, October 12, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Economic press conference, October 17, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Choir concert, Heinz Chapel, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - School of Pharmacy check presentation, October 21, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Minority recruitment conference, October 22, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - Men's basketball coaching staff, October 19, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - PT reception, October 20, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Women's basketball, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Graduate School of Public Health students, October 24, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Parents' Day, October 24, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Men's basketball, October 26, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Jazz performers presentation, November 4, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Power of Partnerships symposium, November 5, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Visiting law professor, November 7, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Human engineering lab, December 2, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - School of Health and Rehabilitation Science Christmas party, December 9, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Engineering co-op lunch, November 29, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Family House day of caring, September 1, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Bike fair, September 27, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - New food area, September 27, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Stat communication, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Rich Lush, November 3, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Jim McAuley, November 3, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - School of Engineering plaque presentation, November 8, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Wrestling team, November 7, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Western Psychiatric Institute and Clinic (WPIC) monograph, November 21, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - David Satcher, November 15, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Masters of Business Administration graduation, November 8, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Staff recognition, December 13, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Men's basketball team, November 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - School of Engineering honors college, November 14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Amy Linshigler, November 15, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - Freshmen, November 18, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Wheelchair tour, November 29, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - College fair, November 20, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - School of Pharmacy check presentation, November 30, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Blue and Gold Society handing out gifts at Family House, December 6, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - Children's holiday party, December 10, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - Rick Santorum at Katz Graduate School of Business, December 8, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Stadium renovations, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Woman with art, December 15, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - University Police Patch, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Phone with blue lights, December 16, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Men's basketball, December 21, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Patty's grandma, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Center for Emergency Medicine, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Red Tail Hawk on the Cathedral lawn, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Women's gymnastics, January 14, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 101)
    - United Faculty press conference, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 102)
    - Freshman move in, December 9, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 103)
    - University signs on Fifth Avenue, August 25, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 104)
    - Freshman carnival, August 28, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 105)
    - School of Pharmacy dinner, March 22, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 106)
    - Dr. Levi Walker and Dr. Timothy Carlos, April 19, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 107)
    - Messer lecture at Scaife Hall, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 108)
    - Flying Solo book cover, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 109)
    - Eilene Israel, May 3, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 110)
    - Dr. Joseph Trompeter, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 111)
    - Men's soccer, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 112)
    - Graduate School of Public Health building, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 113)
    - Football trainers, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 114)
    - Critical Care brochure, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 115)
    - David Lawrence, room 211, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 116)
    - School of Medicine homecoming, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 117)
    - Housing team, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 118)
    - Maryann Fralic Lecture series, October 25, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 119)
    - Football team, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - Women's basketball, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 121)
    - Law school graduation, May 26, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - Health care reform hearings with Senator Arlen Specter, January 5, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 123)
    - Dr. Wishwa Kapoor, January 6, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 124)
    - Dr. Wishwa Kapoor, November 8, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 125)
    - Susan Wesmiller, July 3, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 126)
    - Dr. Lidz, January 11, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 127)
    - Dr. Per Basse, January 12, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 128)
    - Lab photos for annual report, January 12, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 129)
    - Pitt Alumni Association, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 130)
    - Ambassadors meeting, January 17, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 131)
    - Katz Graduate School of Business staff, January 27, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 132)
    - Clifford Brubaker (School of Health and Rehabilitation Science), January 26, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 133)
    - Chris Chase, January 24, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 134)
    - Students and Alumni, Match Day, March 15, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 135)
    - Panther Ad, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 136)
    - Nursing reception, March 13, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 137)
    - Dr. Carol Anderson, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 138)
    - Edison Montgomery, January 27, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Unified Storage, 2002-2005; II.; (40 volumes)
  This series contains photographs taken by various CIDDE photographers between January 2002 and October 2005. Subjects include: Portraits, Convocations, visit of President George W. Bush, Picnics, Luncheons, Dinners, Graduations, Lecture Laureate Programs, Southside Complex, Sports, Press Conferences, Panel Discussions, Alumni Events, Dean Scholarship Ball, Retirement Receptions, Coaches and Coach Family Shots, Heinz Lecture Series, Awards Dinners, Campus Stock Photographs, Cameos of Caring, Schenley Park, Petersen Event Center, Peregrine Falcon, Board of Trustee Events, Team Pittsburgh, Pitt Magazine, A.W. Mellon Distinguished Lectures Series, Posvar Training Sessions, Teaching Times, Media Day, Distinguished Teaching Awards, Homecoming, White Coat Ceremony, Fanfest, Arrival Survival, Lantern Night, Panther Night, Pitt Remembers, Move In Day, Day of Caring, Provost's Lecture Series, Check Presentations, Reunions, Networking Events, Jazz Concerts, Foreign Dignitaries, Deans, Dedications, Benedum Hall, Debates, Theatre, Teplitz Memorial Moot Courtroom, Blue and Gold Society, September 11 Remembrance, Nationality Rooms, National Council of Jewish Women, Heisman Trophy, visit of Miss America 2003, visit of K. Leroy Irvis, Elmer H. Grimm Sr. Pharmacy Museum, Heinz Field, Light Up Night, and Kennywood.
- Stock Photographs, 1986-2001; III.; (11 binders and one records box)
  This series contains photographs taken by various CIDDE photographers between 1986 and 2001. The subjects include: Miscellaneous and Stock Slides (9 binders and 1 misc. box), Cathedral of Learning Stock Slides, Chatauqua at Pitt (3 binders), Discovery Weekend, Sports, Football, The Last Game at Pitt Stadium, First Day at Heinz Field, Foster Project, Law Professor Portraits, and University Buildings.